<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gleb Skibitsky</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Gleb Skibitsky</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uses</title><link>/uses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 17:46:32 +0300</pubDate><guid>/uses/</guid><description>This page describes software and hardware I use. Other people also do such lists. I don&amp;rsquo;t know why.
Hardware MacBook Pro 15 Planck Ez Razer Deathadder iPhone 8 Plus AirPods Pro and Marshall Major II Raspberry Pi Zero to host Pi Hole(https://github.com/pi-hole/pi-hole) and Pi 4 for other things Nintendo Switch Browsers Safari — my main browser. It&amp;rsquo;s fast and respects privacy. Firefox - amazing open-source browser. I would use it as my main browser if it had a level of synchronisation between Mac and iPhone that Safari has Lagrange - open source gemini client Productivity Things 3 - my task management system.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>/projects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 12:04:51 +0300</pubDate><guid>/projects/</guid><description>Most of projects I&amp;rsquo;m working on as a developer are still under NDA, but I enjoy building open-source tools in my spare time. Here is a small list of them. Also, you can follow me on GitHub or stalk my activity on Gitstalk.
Open Source Projects Unity Now → ▲ Zeit Now plugin for Unity. Deploy WebGL builds with ease.
Awesome Stars → A curated list of my GitHub 500+ stars sorted by languages.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 16:59:46 +0200</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Hi, I am Gleb 👋
I am a maker, working mostly on Unity stuff.
Values As libertarian, I stand for equal rights, freedom of expression and NAP. In people, I value liberty, creativity, and dedication.
Projects Planing to make a nice-looking &amp;ldquo;My Projects&amp;rdquo; page on this website to write about all cool things I worked on. Meanwhile, you can check out my GitHub for open-source projects or LinkedIn for formal experience.</description></item></channel></rss>